(Sheldon:)So, yes, I'll go to your dopey play.
- Hey, I don't want you to go anymore.
- Why not?
Go because you want to,
not because you have to.
(Sheldon:)Oh, dear Lord, more rules.
Where does it stop?
(Sheldon:)Can I want to go
because I have to want to go?
- Okay, do whatever you want.
- Yeah, but, no, wait.
(Sheldon:)Do whatever I want
or whatever I have to want?
(Penny:)Oh, for God's sake, just come to the play.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Sheldon:)I don't want to
but at least that makes sense.
(Sheldon:)You know, I haven't seen Raj
in several days.
(Sheldon:)Is he no longer a part of our social group?
(Sheldon:)And if so, should we be
interviewing for a replacement?
(Sheldon:)Perhaps this time we go Latin.